

Chukwuemeka Remigius

MERN stack and Solidity Programmer.

Location: Enugu

Phone: +2348160564759

Email: chuksremi15@gmail.com

Github: https://github.com/chuksremi15 Portfolio: https://chuksremyblog.web.app/ Linkedin: click to redirect to linkedin

Full-stack and blockchain programmer with over 4 years of experience. Solid skills in HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Redux, Node.js, Solidity. Experienced project team lead. Willing to learn and improve along with conventions in the ecosystem. Graduate of Computer Science.

謳 **Technical Skills**

Node.js	4 years	
React	4 years	
Solidity	3 years	
Typescript	4 years	
Redux	4 years	
MongoDB	4 years	
React native	2 years	

Additional skills.

Nextjs

Additional Skills.					
Ethers 3 year	Firebase 4 year	Blockchain 3 year	MySQL 2 year		
Hardhat 3 year	Truffle 3 year	Web3.js 3 year	Express.js 4 year		
TailwindCss 3 y	ear AWS 3 year	Docker 3 year	Postgresql 2 year		

Work History

Frontend Programmer at Canary Tech December 2019 - December 2021 | 2 years

2 years

Canary tech is the parent company of parapay, a fintech startup.

- Collaborated with a team of two developers in building the fintech app. Integrated Web API's to frontend Applications.
- Worked with Chakra UI, Sass, Redux-saga.
- Developed Admin front end using react and redux-saga for state management

The product has handled more than 1 billion naira in transactions

January 2022 - June 2022 | 6 months

Full-stack Blockchain Programmer at Omitch

Omitch is a casino start-up on the blockchain

Responsible for the full cycles of the blockchain development which include

- writing smart contracts, writing tests, and integrating ABIs to frontend. Converted casino business logic to code.
- Integrated games from a gaming provider
- Worked with Hardhat, Mocha, Chai, Ethers, and Web3js.

September 2022 - December 2023 | 1 year 4 months

MERN stack dev at Al Movement

Al Movement is a community of private investors, institutional investors,

and technology experts. I worked as the CTO at Al Movement, with a small team of one frontend programmer and a UI/UX person. Responsible for the full cycles of the application development which include

- writing code, writing tests, and inspecting all code base. • Drawing out system architecture/blueprints for projects.
- Ensuring smooth functionality of our app and fixing bugs Worked with React, Express.js, Redux.

Side projects

ENScheap https://enscheap.vercel.app

Carbon ENS wallet https://carbonenswallet.web.app

Chain link CLI(NPM package) https://www.npmjs.com/package/chainpeekcli

Color city NFT https://colorcity.vercel.app

Multisig smart contract https://supermultisigwallet.surge.sh

Education

December 2017 - December 2021

Nnamdi Azikiwe University BSC in computer science